cellphones.ca 2018-09-03

# Privacy Policy - The Informr

_**  
Protecting your privacy is important to us. The purpose of this Privacy Policy is to help you understand how we collect, use, and share information about you.**_

Last Updated: May 23, 2018

## Who We Are

We are ten24 Media Inc.; a company incorporated in Canada, the registered office of which is 185, 11007 Jasper Avenue NW, Edmonton AB Canada, T5K 0K6, hereinafter "ten24" (also "we" "our" or "us").

ten24 operates several websites including theinformr.com, theinformr.co.uk, theinformr.in, www.cellphones.ca.

By accessing or using the Services, you agree to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Service.

## What Is Personal Data

Personal data means any information relating to an identified or identifiable person. This includes, for example, your name, e-mail address and IP address.

## What Information We Collect About You and Why

What types of information we collect from you depends on how you use our website and what information you choose to provide.

We collect information from you when you:

  * Visit our websites or download any of our files
  * Create or register an account, modify your profile, set preferences, sign-up for offers or make purchases. (For example, we require individuals to provide their email address and a username when they register for an account. You also have the option of adding your real name, profile photo, location, and other details to be displayed on our Websites–but we don’t require that information to create an account.)
  * Add questions, comments, reviews, and other messages on our community forums, via web forms, email, or other methods
  * Contact us via email
  * Participate in any promotions, demonstrations, contests, surveys, or other marketing events

If you have an account with us, we collect the information that you provide for your public profile. For example, if you have an Informr account, your username / display name is part of that public profile, along with any other information you voluntarily put into your public profile, such as a photo or an “About Me” description.

Your public profile information is just that–public–so please keep that in mind when deciding what information you would like to include.

We may collect information about your web browser or device, including your IP address, information about your visit (including how you came to the site and the name of the website you visit when you leave our website), and how you use our site. 

We use this information to help improve our website, communicate with you, provide support, personalize your experience and to market, promote and drive engagement with our services.

Third party services we use may also collect information about our website visitors. Examples of services we currently use include [Google Analytics](https://analytics.google.com/) and [Google AdSense](https://www.google.com/adsense/)on this website.

### Community Forums / Comments

Our websites offer publicly accessible reviews, comments or community forums (questions/answers).

You should be aware that any information you provide in these areas may be read, collected, and used by others who access them.

You should be aware that any information you provide, including your profile information associated with your account, may be read, collected, and used by any member of the public who accesses these websites.

Your profile information and posts may remain even after you delete your account. Never post any personal financial information or other sensitive information into these public forums. When visitor's post on the site, we collect the data shown in the form, and also the visitor’s IP address and browser user agent string to help spam detection.

An anonymized string created from your email address (also called a hash) may be provided to the Gravatar service to see if you are using it.

The Gravatar service privacy policy is available here: <https://automattic.com/privacy/>. Your profile picture is visible to the public in the context of your comment.

### Media

If you upload images to the website, you should avoid uploading images with embedded location data (EXIF GPS) included. Visitors to the website can download and extract any location data from images on the website.

### Contact Forms

When you contact us via the contact form on this website, the information is sent as email messages that only a select few are allowed to access. The information is also stored in the database on our hosting server for backup and later reference purposes.

### Location Information

In some cases, we may collect limited location information from your IP address or information you volunteer. For example, we may use Google Analytics convert your IP address into a rough geolocation to understand in what areas our users are located and to improve and personalize our website (for example, to display the nearest retailers or to show services in available in your region).

* * *

## Cookies & Other Tracking Technologies

Like many websites, we use cookies and similar technologies to collect additional usage data and to improve our Services, but we do not require cookies for many parts of our Services such as viewing product information and reading community discussions.

A cookie is a string of information that a website stores on a visitor’s computer, and that the visitor’s browser provides to the website each time the visitor returns. Pixel tags (also called web beacons) are small blocks of code placed on websites and emails.

We use cookies and other technologies like pixel tags to help us identify and track visitors, usage, and access preferences for our Services, as well as track and understand email campaign effectiveness and to deliver targeted ads.

If your browser is configured to accept cookies, we may collect non-personally identifiable information passively using "cookies" and "page tags".

If you leave a question or comment on our site you may opt-in to saving your name, email address and website in cookies.

These are for your convenience so that you do not have to fill in your details again when you leave another comment. These cookies will last for one year.

If you have an account and you log in to this site, we will set a temporary cookie to determine if your browser accepts cookies. This cookie contains no personal data and is discarded when you close your browser.

When you log in, we will also set up several cookies to save your login information. Login cookies last for sixty days.

If you edit or publish a post (ie. comments, reviews, questions, answers), an additional cookie will be saved in your browser. This cookie includes no personal data and simply indicates the post ID of the post you just edited.

### Embedded Content From Other Websites

Articles on this site may include embedded content (e.g. videos, images, articles, etc.). Embedded content from other websites behaves in the exact same way as if the visitor has visited the other website. These websites may collect data about you, use cookies, embed additional third-party tracking, and monitor your interaction with that embedded content, including tracing your interaction with the embedded content if you have an account and are logged in to that website.

### Analytics

We use third party analytics services such as Google Analytics and these services use cookies, web beacons, and other tracking technologies to collect information such as your IP address, time of visit, whether you are a return visitor, and any referring website, in order to help us analyze and create reports on how users interact with and use our services.

The information we collect from analytics helps us understand what parts of our sites are doing well, how people arrive at our site and so on.

Like most websites, we use this information to make our website better.

We collect non-personal information through our Internet log files, which record data such as browser types, domain names, and other anonymous statistical data involving the use of our Services.

### Advertising

We will never provide Advertisers with access to your name, address, e-mail address, or telephone number without your explicit consent.

We may use your Personal Information to provide you with targeted advertisements or marketing communications we believe may be of interest to you. For more information about how targeted advertising works, you can visit the Network Advertising Initiative’s (“NAI”) educational page at <http://www.networkadvertising.org/understanding-online-advertising/how-does-it-work>.

Third-party vendors, including Google and Facebook, use cookies web beacons, and other tracking technologies to serve ads that may be of interest to you. Any data collected will be subject to their respective privacy policies (which we do not control and for which we are not responsible). You can opt-out of targeted advertising by visiting the links below: [Google](https://support.google.com/ads/answer/2662922?hl=en) [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/ads/website_custom_audiences/) [Bing](https://advertise.bingads.microsoft.com/en-us/resources/policies/personalized-ads)

### How Do I Find, Manage or Delete My Cookies?

Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but also usually allow you to modify your settings to disable or reject cookies.

The steps you need to take to manage your cookies will depend on the browser you’re using. Below are links to instructions on how to manage cookies for the most common browsers:

[](https://support.apple.com/en-ie/guide/safari/manage-cookies-and-website-data-sfri11471/mac/)If you delete your cookies or if you set your web browser to decline cookies, however, some features of the website may not work or may not work as designed.

* * *

## Emails

We may send you email notifications regarding your account or for other communications you have specifically requested (such as newsletters or notifications when someone replies to one of your comments).

You have the ability to opt out of any of this communication at any time. We will never provide your personal information or email address to any third parties except where they are specifically employed to help deliver our own services.

## Newsletters / Marketing Communications

Where you have given us consent, we may contact you by email about our products and services (including from all our brands). If you would like to opt-out of receiving such communications from us, you can click the unsubscribe link at the bottom of any emails you receive, or email us at privacy(at)theinformr(dot)com, stating your preferences.

## Who We Share Your Data With

We may share your personal data with:

  * to our own affiliated companies
  * to third party agents and vendors who perform functions on our behalf, including, but not limited to, hosting, content syndication, content management tools, social media integration, marketing, analytics, billing and customer service
  * to third party content or advertising partners
  * if we are legally entitled or required to do so
  * if we sell the business or part of it to another company

This Privacy Statement does not cover third-party content, apps or websites you access or use through our website. We do not control the privacy and security practices or policies of these third parties and their apps/sites.

We encourage you to read the privacy statements which apply to the third-party content, apps and websites you use. Here is a list of some of the third parties that we may use:  

  * [Google Analytics](https://policies.google.com/privacy) \- analytics services
  * [Amazon Web Services](https://aws.amazon.com/privacy) \- image / file hosting
  * [Rackspace Web](https://www.rackspace.com/information/legal/privacystatement) \- hosting
  * [Google AdSense](https://www.google.com/adsense/new/localized-terms) \- advertising
  * [Facebook](https://www.facebook.com/policy.php) \- marketing
  * [Sumo](https://help.sumo.com/hc/en-us/articles/218958727-Privacy-Policy) \- sharing
  * [SendGrid](https://sendgrid.com/policies/privacy/) \- email services

You can log in to our websites using sign-in services such as Facebook Connect or an OAuth provider. These services will authenticate your identity and provide you the option to share certain personal information with us such as your name and email address to pre-populate our sign up form.

Services like Facebook Connect give you the option to post information about your activities on this Web site to your profile page to share with others within your network.

Third-party websites and services we link to are outside our control. We are not responsible for the security or privacy of any information collected by these third parties, which operate pursuant to their respective privacy policies.

## How Long We Retain Your Data

If you leave a comment, the comment and its metadata are retained indefinitely. This is so we can recognize and approve any follow-up comments automatically instead of holding them in a moderation queue. For users that register on our website (if any), we also store the personal information they provide in their user profile. All users can see, edit, or delete their personal information at any time (except they cannot change their username). Website administrators can also see and edit that information.

## What Rights You Have Over Your Data

If you have an account on this site, or have left comments, you have the right to access personal information we hold about you and to ask that your personal information be corrected, updated, or deleted.

If you would like to exercise this right, please contact us through the contact information below.

Additionally, if you are a European resident we note that we are processing your information in order to fulfill contracts we might have with you (for example if you make an order through the Site), or otherwise to pursue our legitimate business interests listed above.

Additionally, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

## Where We Send Your Data

Visitor comments may be checked through an automated spam detection service. If you are a European resident, please note that your information will be transferred outside of Europe, including to Canada and the United States.

## How We Protect Your Data

We care about your privacy, and provide appropriate security measures to protect your information. We have implemented organizational and technical procedures and measures that will ensure that your personal data is not compromised, not unintentionally changed, and available when required.

Unfortunately, no security measures are 100% foolproof and we cannot guarantee 100% security of the information we collect and store. If you believe your information may not be secure for any reason, please contact us immediately at privacy(at)theinformr(dot)com.

## Information for Parents

Our websites are not directed to anyone under the age of 13. If you are under 13 years old and you wish to use our website in any way which requires you to submit your personal data, please get your parent or legal guardian to do so on your behalf.

## Privacy Policy Changes

Although most changes are likely to be minor, this privacy policy may change from time to time, and in our sole discretion. We encourages visitors to frequently check this page for any changes. Your continued use of this site after any change in this Privacy Policy will constitute your acceptance of such change.

## Conditions of Use

If you decide to visit our websites, your visits and any possible dispute over privacy is subject to this Privacy Policy and our Terms of Use, including limitations on damages, arbitration of disputes, and application of Canadian law.

## Contact information

If you would like more information about our privacy practices or:

  * wish to request access to information we hold about you, correct, modify, delete or update personal data that you have provided to us, or
  * have any questions regarding this Privacy Policy, wish to withdraw your consent for the continued collection, would like to object to your personal data being used, or have any additional questions

Please contact us via email: **privacy(at)theinformr(dot)com**  or by mail using the details provided below:

ten24 Media Inc.   
185, 11007 Jasper Avenue NW   
Edmonton, AB   
T5K 0K6
